Aviv Moyal

Software Engineering Student

Studying software engineering in Shenkar. Self-starting and motivated individual. Highly adaptable and a fast

learner. With 3 years in the hospitality industry, I developed a wide-ranging skill set at sales, and cultivating strong customer relationships.

Contact

Address

Givatayim Katznelson 71, Israel, 53270

Phone

054 726 6430

E-mail

avivmoyal1@gmail.com

Software

Office	Excellent
С	Good
C++	Good
Python	Basic

Skills

Technology oriented

Customer service

Time management

Teamwork



Work History

2018-07 -2021-09

Telemarketing Sales Representative

Isrotel, Eilat

- customize the best deal to the customer needs and budget
- working with individual and companies closing deals up to 130K NIS
- Provide existing customers support and increase sales
- Establishing relationships with Isrotel club member to increase sales

2017-01 -2018-01

Waiter

Ranch house, Eilat

- Work under pressure serving up to 100 guests at a time
- Team work, learn how to work as a unit
- Establishing relationships with customers in order to increase sales

2016-01 -2017-01

Waiter

El gaochu, Eilat

- work under pressure serving up to 150 guests at a time
- team work, learn how to work as a unit
- •

Languages

Hebrew

Excellent

English

Good

Education

2010-03 -2012-07

High School Diploma

Arya Meit School - Kiryat Gat

School Diploma grade - 94

- Art 5 units
- communication and radio 7 units

Volunteered

2017 -

IGY - Israel Gay Youth

2020

In my position as a counselor i provide a safe space for LGBT youth by conducting meetings and activities around the LGBT community

Army service

2013 -2016 Course guide

I served full 3 years as a communication equipment guide.

In duty I were to preform a 2 mounts course for new recruits in groups of 10-20 soldiers at a time, during the course I was required to:

- Creating a lesson plan
- Teaching equipment handling and maintenance
- Attend soldiers at class and daily needs